<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story10_part_0">
		<text>Remember, Duchmans, there's no rustle or movement, it doesn't bother you, you just calmly drop the horn on the sector and hit the bushes and trees, you'll blow your horn and you fall behind cover on your back, the controller hooks up if he sees you and then he needs time to adjust on the victim, while you're sunbathing on your back flipping and you put the short bursts on the mate and you put the short bursts on the gun Patron, you count for three, you go for three, you go for three, you go for three from there, sucking up information, suckers, be like me, you'll live to see demobiles </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story11_part_0">
		<text>Shelden, long story short, one of the bushkas told me, there's a cool place, cool, artefacts kinda stash someone's stash. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story11_part_1">
		<text>So I pushed the door, it was closed. What's the matter, it's closed again. So I open her bitch, and she bitch closes herself. I realised that someone wasn't letting me through the door. Well, I went through the window. Inside, I took a breath, recovered a little, went to see who was it's the one with the door. And there's a big room with a long table in it, like a motorway, and by the table there's a desk as tall as a turret. And then someone whispered in my head, and the sheh went. Who are you asking? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story11_part_2">
		<text>I said, Vanya, I'm from here, every dog here knows me, she whispered again. He says, Vanya, why are you poking around the zone? Why are you climbing through the window? I'm not confused, I said. So, I went in for a drink of water, I saw no-one was there, so I went in. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story11_part_3">
		<text>It says, "How about some water? No, Uanya, there's no water. And you don't need it anymore. Well, shit, I'm just saying, how? Well, if there's no water, I'm out of here. So I tried chipping from there, real quick. It's all the same, or some creature, it's not talking to me. Or a white fever, and it's time to get out of the zone. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story11_part_4">
		<text>It says, "Wait a minute, Vanya, stay here, I have something to do with you. I can't move my feet off the floor. It's telling me there's something wrong with your head, I'm gonna give you I can barely feel it. Why am I asking, I need to feel, I don't need to feel to feel me. It's again, that's what it's all about. I can smell guys like you from 200 metres away, but you're only just before the door, only after you've you started breaking in. Do you have any new specialised equipment? What kind of equipment do I have? I said I don't have anything. The torch here, yeah, it's an old double-helmet. That's all the equipment. I've never had anything like this before, Citizen Warden. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story11_part_5">
		<text>It says, you're not my rebbe, I can see right through you, don't bring me to sin. I said, "I don't even have a God, even if you search me. It whispered, and this one can do it. Then my body started to rumble, everything in my pockets started to crawl out, started to crawl out on its own. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story11_part_6">
		<text>And, most importantly, the coveted chekuska, too. Well, I think the bastards are not me, I won't give you my family. It's a long day's walk, but I'm not gonna make it. I clutched the bottle to the baby. It's mine, Citizen Warden. And the bottle is like someone holding a bottle. And it won't let go, it's pulling upwards. Well, I guess you'll never get my moonshine, you bastard. He pulled the bottle towards him, pulled the cork out with his teeth, and began to drink. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story11_part_7">
		<text>I barely took three sips, I couldn't get it down, my throat felt like a vise, my eyes are already spinning in circles. So, I took five more sips, probably through and through, threw a bottle at them, choking on it, you bastards. That's when I let go. And it says this. Where did you go, Vanya? Where did you disappear to? I haven't disappeared, Citizen Warden, I'm telling you. I'm crawling away. Oh, here we go again. Don't be stupid, Vanya, if I catch you, it'll be worse. That's when I realised. Although the first one gave me a good kick in the head, the bitch lost sight of me. It's got to flow. Barely got to my feet, everything swaying like a nine-point bulk carrier. So I go to the window, I lie back, nails are flying in the room. My stuff from the pockets that bricks drop from above. And shooping, cursing in my wake. I'll get it, Kevanya, I'll get it, I'll get it. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story11_part_8">
		<text>So, I jumped out of the window and went. The stuff, the rjo, it's all left there. How I got out of the zone drunk, God knows. But I'm not going out of there now. That neighbourhood. I'm dead, but I'm not going. I'm thinking maybe we should go to Cuchon's. It's been a long time coming. Rjo, footy. All the stuff's gone, where's it all going. Bitch. That's what happened to me. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story1_part_0">
		<text>By the way, have you heard? They say that everything that happens in the zone, is of unearthly origin, like an alien experiment on humans. The young critters are preparing a beachhead for an invasion and are working out plans here in the zone like a training ground. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story1_part_1">
		<text>They say, for example, that artefacts are bombs that will detonate at one point. And so they're wasted on labs, a bunch of Earth's scientific resources will be destroyed. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story1_part_2">
		<text>You may not believe it, but who knows, maybe someone's went behind the radar and can tell you who really saw the healthy place of stalkers who came back from it. We're chatting something, drooling. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story1_part_3">
		<text>That's why I'm having these thoughts. I'm thinking maybe those freak aliens on the site of the radar have put up some sort of defence field of their own, which wipes your brains out like our DAC, huh? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story2_part_0">
		<text>Dudes! Has anyone heard of any highly classified labs deep in the zone. They say they still work. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story2_part_1">
		<text>How people were able to survive there and after the explosion is unknown? With no supplies, no energy, and the question arises, are people if they're working there or if it's definitely alien crap sitting there? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story2_part_2">
		<text>I've been having a chat. He said he never saw it in the lab, but he caught it once he's making strange radio conversations on the entor. They were talking about some lab, and one dude was talking about he swore he saw a translucent figure in a spacesuit like Stalker's, well, more sophisticated, and this figure told him to get the hell out of here. Like, don't bother us, we're working here. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story2_part_3">
		<text>Well, the guy's shitting himself, obviously. He's never seen anything like this before. True, he claimed it was on the radar. Well, you know. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story2_part_4">
		<text>so it's unlikely to be true, of course. But I'm thinking that if at the moment the zones went off, What if she transferred these people into some kind of energy entities, like new people? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story3_part_0">
		<text>Have you heard of the conductor? He was the first stalker to go to the zone. And seems to be able to lead just about anywhere in the zone. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story3_part_1">
		<text>The other thing is that finding it is very problematic. And they say he doesn't agree to see everyone. Takes a lot of money. But if you find him and make a deal, you can be sure he's getting you to the right spot in the zone. I'd love to talk to him. Jon saw what's behind the radar. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story4_part_0">
		<text>Have you heard the legend of the dark stalker? Рђ? Shit. I'm afraid to tell her. It was told to me by a veteran in great secrecy, but a day later, he disappeared without a trace. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story4_part_1">
		<text>Maybe I will, if I tell her. I'll be dead tomorrow. No, dudes, I won't. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story5_part_0">
		<text>Did you hear that? You can't sleep in the zone. You can have nightmares so bad, you might not wake up. Somebody gets heartbroken in their sleep, like a horse moving, or you could just go nuts. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story5_part_1">
		<text>But they say that if you need to sleep, it's on your head you have to wear a helmet with a net and a thin wire. And it'll all work out. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story5_part_2">
		<text>By the way, they say that military stalkers wearing these helmets walking. There's some kind of tacos on them. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story6_part_0">
		<text>By the way, here it was. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story6_part_1">
		<text>Approaching and the boundaries of the zone. I take out my wire cutters beforehand and head for the wire to the fence. Here Vasil looked at me, so Lukawa says. I'll bet I can do a nascence pass in 7 actions. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story6_part_2">
		<text>So I'll get it right away, and I'll say, and I'll go for six, and I'll go for five, for four, for one. I'm thinking to myself, how is he going to exist? Well, I say go ahead and do it. This pretzel calmly removes the grenade and slams it under the fence. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story6_part_3">
		<text>I've got one of these, and he says don't, and slaps the dirt with his nose. Vasily, flop next to me. What's up, bang? We've been hit so hard with dirt. Overhead, this sign flew over my head, it's dangerous not to approach. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story6_part_4">
		<text>Anyway, I grab Vasily by the belt, we run. You know, there's a lot of people from the roadblock right now will come running with machine guns. We dashed across the draw fence, the watering can, the nearest groves. We got there, collapsed in the hole, breathing, listening. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story6_part_5">
		<text>And those from machine-guns, on us, of course, from above all sorts of noise, chips, lumps. You know what I mean, don't you? Well, that's where I tell Vasili. I bet I'll punch you in the face the first time. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story7_part_0">
		<text>I'm recently looking in the mint, in the ground is distinctive, trampoline like. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story7_part_1">
		<text>I'm sure I'm throwing a bolt and I'm freaking out. The bolt's going to fucking fly, but I'm thinking A glitch. I drank too much alcohol while I was in the zone The ground is lighter and the edges are flattened. The wind pulls the leaves from there spiral </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story7_part_2">
		<text>Okay, so he sat down, took a pebble of earth and threw it on the vesicom. Well, I think it stinks. Breathe. The pebble fell quietly to the ground as if it wasn't there no anomaly. He just fell down. Well, I'm sweating. My gut tells me it's a mansion. I'm squatting on my hands and knees. I'm throwing pebbles, it's a fucking reflex. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story7_part_3">
		<text>Under the pols wouldn't believe it, up close, sweaty as a mouse mbezi. The reeds I left lay neatly in the bald spot. But my stalker gut has to go. I don't, mansion, we need to figure it out. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story7_part_4">
		<text>So I put the bagpipe on my lap, and I'm fucking pulling hand in the springboard, to one of the rocks. Come to think of it, eh? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story7_part_5">
		<text>took a pebble like a pebble and that's where it worked. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story7_part_6">
		<text>But I was thrown about five metres away. Haya, of course, touched the pebble. The puddle's working. While I was still flying, I saw the rocks in the dust. Bumped, passed out. But I, Entodus, have carried the stone with me ever since. That's it. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story8_part_0">
		<text>Did you hear that? Krupp turned round. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story8_part_1">
		<text>Lugovoi is dead, I'll open from Lianev's brain, the rest are in intensive care. Shit, basically. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story8_part_2">
		<text>Stepanok under the drip, Fedin that one concussed. If it wasn't him, by the way, they'd all be buried, and even the ejection there wasn't. Pulling the artefact container now from Tikhonych. His team of physicists are testing it on instruments. Preliminary word is that it's anomaly debris, some sort of encapsulated in some sort of torsion field. Denser than uranium by about half. Plus some kind of psychon-level artefact ripple. The properties are, of course, obscure. Tikhonich is silent as a partisan. Mathew's Pulsation. Yes. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story9_part_0">
		<text>A year and a half ago, a stalker, Kostya Fidorich may remember, stumbled across an artefact. Rubble to rubble. But he didn't throw it away, he had a gut feeling. Carried the zone around with him like a talisman in a people's pocket. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story9_part_1">
		<text>The guys who went with him say the zone loved him, let him go far, but as it later turned out not so much. It's on the radar and it's gone. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_story9_part_2">
		<text>I wonder who picked up the artefact now? Shvenov knows. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_action_right_1">
		<text>That's right! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_action_right_2">
		<text>Well done! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_action_right_3">
		<text>That's the way to do it! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_action_right_4">
		<text>Makes sense. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_action_right_5">
		<text>That's right, mate! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_action_wrong_1">
		<text>It's a waste! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_action_wrong_2">
		<text>You shouldn't have! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_action_wrong_3">
		<text>Well, that's just wrong. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_action_wrong_4">
		<text>You shouldn't have done that. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_advice_sceptic_1">
		<text>Fuck you, Salabonov! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_advice_sceptic_2">
		<text>Heh-heh-heh! You'll scare the salak away! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_advice_sceptic_3">
		<text>Come on, you'll scare away all the newbies. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_advice_sceptic_4">
		<text>Enough with the newbies. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_advice_support_1">
		<text>That's right! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_advice_support_2">
		<text>That's right, man. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_advice_support_3">
		<text>Dude's got a point. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_advice_support_4">
		<text>Yes, it's experienced. Son, mistakes are hard to make. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_belief_story_1">
		<text>It happens. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_belief_story_2">
		<text>Yeah, anything can happen. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_belief_story_3">
		<text>There's a lot of things that happen. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_belief_story_4">
		<text>on all sorts of things. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_continue_1">
		<text>So what? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_continue_2">
		<text>What's next? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_continue_3">
		<text>Well? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_continue_4">
		<text>So. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_continue_5">
		<text>Hey! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_continue_6">
		<text>Writing. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_info_1">
		<text>Whoa! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_info_2">
		<text>Holy shit! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_info_3">
		<text>NOTHING! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_info_4">
		<text>Wow! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_info_5">
		<text>Holy shit! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_info_6">
		<text>Nice! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_info_7">
		<text>Cool! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_teller_1">
		<text>Oh, come on. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_teller_2">
		<text>MALLACE! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_teller_3">
		<text>You're awesome, man! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_cool_teller_4">
		<text>Cool! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_1">
		<text>Oh, come on! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_2">
		<text>You're delusional. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_3">
		<text>What doesn't happen when you're drunk? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_4">
		<text>I don't believe it. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_5">
		<text>It sounds like drunken ramblings. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_1">
		<text>And it's all bollocks. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_10">
		<text>I don't believe it. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_11">
		<text>That's ridiculous. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_2">
		<text>GONEVA </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_3">
		<text>Yeah, right. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_4">
		<text>I don't believe it. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_5">
		<text>Here's another one. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_6">
		<text>Fairy tales </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_7">
		<text>Bollocks! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_8">
		<text>What a load of rubbish. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_story_9">
		<text>It sounds like drunken ramblings. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_1">
		<text>You're full of shit! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_10">
		<text>Oh, come on! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_11">
		<text>What doesn't happen when you're drunk? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_2">
		<text>can't be </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_3">
		<text>Stop pouring! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_4">
		<text>Oh, come on! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_5">
		<text>Lie more! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_6">
		<text>I'm rocking a noodle! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_7">
		<text>Stop messing around. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_8">
		<text>Fucking stars! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_disbelief_teller_9">
		<text>Go to hell! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_doubt_1">
		<text>Oh, I doubt it! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_doubt_2">
		<text>I don't believe it. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_doubt_3">
		<text>I don't know, I don't believe it. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_doubt_4">
		<text>DANU! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_fear_1">
		<text>Dibs on me! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_fear_2">
		<text>Toot-toot-toot! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_happy_1">
		<text>That's lucky, that's lucky. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_happy_2">
		<text>All's well that ends well. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_happy_3">
		<text>These are the lucky ones. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_happy_4">
		<text>Lucky. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_happy_5">
		<text>Some people are lucky. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_tragic_1">
		<text>Yeah, bad luck. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_tragic_2">
		<text>Oh, man. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_tragic_3">
		<text>What grief! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_tragic_4">
		<text>Peda in a word. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_tragic_5">
		<text>Hey, hey, hey... </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_final_tragic_6">
		<text>We're all gonna die! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_1">
		<text>Ha ha ha! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_10">
		<text>Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_2">
		<text>Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_3">
		<text>Heh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_4">
		<text>Quickly! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_5">
		<text>Ha ha ha! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_6">
		<text>Ha ha ha! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_7">
		<text>Heh-heh-heh-heh-heh! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_8">
		<text>Heh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_laughter_9">
		<text>Missing_Subtitle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_old_story_1">
		<text>Oh, I've heard that before. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_old_story_2">
		<text>Slashle. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_uncertain_1">
		<text>Fuck knows! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_uncertain_2">
		<text>The hell you will. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_uncertain_3">
		<text>Madin Allah knows. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_wonder_1">
		<text>Holy shit! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_wonder_2">
		<text>I'm freaking out! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_wonder_3">
		<text>Holy shit! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_wonder_4">
		<text>No way! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_wonder_5">
		<text>This can't be happening! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_wonder_6">
		<text>DANU! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_wonder_7">
		<text>Oh, really? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_yes_1">
		<text>That's right. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_yes_2">
		<text>Which yes, it is. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_yes_3">
		<text>That's right. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_yes_4">
		<text>Mm-hmm. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_yes_5">
		<text>Mm-hmm. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_yes_6">
		<text>Yeah. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_yes_7">
		<text>Yes... </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_yes_8">
		<text>That's for sure. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_story_reactions_yes_9">
		<text>Mm-hmm. </text>
	</string>
</string_table>