<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- There is nothing in this audio file -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Missing_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Slightly changed phrase, but not really sure about it-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>Anyway, here's what! </text> // contracted statement 
	</string>
	<!-- Slight correction in the end -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>Hey, guys. Here's what else I've heard. </text> // slight grammatical edit
	</string>
	<!-- Slight correction -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>Hey, guys. Here's an anecdote! </text> // slight grammatical edit
	</string>
	<!-- slight correction-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>Well, in short! </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Again not sure, but thing this will be better -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_5">
		<text>Quiet! Quiet! So here's what! </text> // slight grammatical edit
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_music_1">
		<text>And now for the soul! </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Word "Sha" basically mean here "Now", midlle word "something", last word means "play"-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_music_2">
		<text>Now I will play something! </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Changed "come on" to "Well"-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_music_3">
		<text>Well; well, well, let me get play something! </text> // slight grammatical edit
	</string>
	<!-- So here only ploblem in uderstanding is because of the word "Labush" most of the time it means a wide-profile musician
	Here I think meaning is "how to play"-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_music_4">
		<text>Let's see now if my hands remember how to play or not. </text> // slight grammatical edit
	</string>
	<!-- So here what I will do, I will translate these jokes in the in the best of my abilities and not explain it here, otherwise what will be point of them -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>One mate asks another mate: "Listen, why did you go to the zone?". "I've escaped from the cops and decided to hide here.". "Duh, what did the police get you for?". "For nothing, I got pulled over, as usual. And everything's wrong with me; numbers dirty, no medkit, ran a red light. Yes, on oncoming traffic. Yeah, backwards! drunk! And with five guns in the boot. So what's up?" </text> // slight grammatical edits, i assume 'wrong with me' part is him listing his violations
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_10">
		<text>There's these real boys driving a BMW around the Zone. So like, they stopped to take a piss, but just when they started—bang—out of the darkness, a Bloodsucker comes out and screams: "I'll suck you!" The guys looked at one another calmly and said: "Thank you bro, but do it in our circle." </text> // slight grammatical edits, i assume bros are thanking each other for bloodsucker head and ask it to get in their circle
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_11">
		<text>Three stalkers meet at the Garbage. One of them has his eye out; the other one has a scarred face, the third have no toes on his feet at all. So they started asking how they got all that beauty from. The first one shows his eye and says "I didn't share the loot with the gyus, had to shoot them." Everyone's just kind of nodding respectfully, okay? The second one's pointing at his face. "I got into fight with a pack of pseudodogs", everyone's like: 'like respect, good job'. They're looking at the third one, who's kind of lost himself and saying nothing. "Hey, mate what happened to your leg?", one's asking. "Well, when I was working at the camp. I wore lead underwear so I wouldn't become impotent from radiation.". "You put them on, so what?". "Well, the elastic got busted." </text> // grammatical edits to make it flow better 
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>One day a brother comes into a bar on Skadovsk and says to Beard: "Hey, bro, give me some booze!" Beard said to him: "A glass of beer or a shot of vodka?". "Damn, a glass of vodka, of course!" </text> // grammatical edits and additions for flow
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>A Stalker returned to the Zone, visited home and complains: "You hear me, I sold an artefact and bought a real car, and after a week it was stolen." Second said to him: "Heck, bad luck. did you go to the police?". "I did. Said it wasn't them.: </text> // slight grammatical edits
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>The mother sends a letter to the real guy in prison. It's like: "Son, as soon as you've gone to prison everythings gone to hell in the household. Spring has already come, we need to dig up the garden there, potatoes and other things to plant. I can't do shit on my own, and no fucking bitch can help me." Well, the guy was like writing to her: "Like, mother, it's for the better, you'd better not touch the garden at all. Survive without it or you're gonna dig up something that's gonna not only increase my sentence, but you'll go to prison too." Mother writes a week later, "Damn Son, after your letter the cops ran to us, dug up the whole garden, only they didn't find shit. They were so angry, saying so many slurs." And the kid replies to her: "Well, Mother, I helped how I can, but you can plant potatoes by yourself." </text> // grammatical edits to better flow
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_5">
		<text>Anyway, two brothers are sitting around talking. One of them says: "Hey, bro, we've been hanging out since we were kids. I'll get you a tattoo for the memory." The other one was like: "Oh, that's a good one. Let's make it like a tank on the spine, but it's gotta be good, got it?". "You're really offending me, you'll like it, I promise you!" After five minutes, the tattoer's like: "Opa! Awesome, it's done!" And the other one: "Huh, I don't get it, why so fast?" tattoer: "I mean, there is only four letters." </text> // grammatical edits
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_6">
		<text>These people are asking: "What? Where? When?" The showman is like: "And now the question will be asked by a real guy, Vovan." Vovan appears on the screen, his face like this: "Honourable experts, two months ago, my mate Kalyan borrowed from me five thousand and didn't pay it back, this bitch! A onth ago, Kalyan borrowed three thousand from me and hasn't paid back, this bitch. A week ago, he only borrowed fifty and that fucking bitch didn't pay back too. So the fucking question is, who the fuck is in the black box?" </text> // grammatical edits
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_7">
		<text>There's these two usual Stalker-Losers standing at the Garbage. One like asks the other: "Hey, I don't get it. We gave them money, Yes. Why'd these boys run away somewhere and aren't dancing?". "Fuck, you blockhead,  I already told you a hundred times! Gopak and gop-stop, are definitely not the same thing! </text> // slight grammatical edits,
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_8">
		<text>The guys caught one Stalker alive, and they telling him: "Oh, like, nice, so we'll have someone to clean up our toilet." And he's, like, a big shot, not afraid, and he says: "Gang, I'm not some bitch or moron for you, Give me something cleaner." Well, the boys talked amongst themselves, and they said: "No problem, man. Go there and get the Goner's stuff from the anomaly." He thought and thought about it, and he said: "So guys—where's this toilet?" </text>  // grammatical edits
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_9">
		<text>Two bloodsuckers are talking with each other, one to the other like: "How do you like to hunt Stalkers." "Well, I notice the Stalker, then I make a big circle around him. Then five minutes of small circles, and only after five more minutes I attack." The first one's like: "Duh, I don't get it. What's the point, mate? Why are you doing these circles? You could immediately have some meat instead." And the other one's like: "No, brother! I didn't get it at first, you can attack immediately, no problem, but then you'd have to eat it with shit." </text> // grammatical edits
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_abuse_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_default_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_fight_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_weapon_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
</string_table>
