<!--
	Locale: English
	Folder: Characters_voice\scenario\bar\arena_megafon
-->
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
    <!-- arena_megafon -->
    <string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_10_sec">
		<text>Ten seconds please, the fight is on!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_20_sec">
		<text>20 seconds please, the fight is on!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_30_sec">
		<text>30 seconds! The fight is on!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_40_sec">
		<text>FORTY SECONDS! THE FIGHT GOES ON!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_50_sec">
		<text>30 seconds! The fight is on!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_60_sec">
		<text>It's been a minute! The fight continues!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_bloodsucker">
		<text>Tonight in the arena is the monstrously bloodthirsty and perpetually hungry CRAVOSOSOS! Against the bloodsucker will be a man, almost a man, and he is not called that for nothing!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_burer">
		<text>Meet the inhabitants of the underground darkness in the arena tonight, that kills at a distance and tears you apart. There are no barriers to it, no defence against it. Some will say it's a horrible underground carny, but I will, that it's Bührer. Against the Bührer will come a hero whose adventures will never end.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_coward">
		<text>You may ask, where is our hero? I'll tell you where! He got scared for his own skin and ran away! Look for this coward at the bar, where he's ducking his sad soul!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_dead">
		<text>Oh my god, lying there not breathing, he's killed, he fought well, but at the last moment, yeah, someone remove the corpse in the charge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_new_fight">
		<text>Attention! Attention! A new fight is about to begin in the arena, that we're going to enjoy thanks to our one and only and a powerful purveyor of monsters MUST!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_out_of_time">
		<text>Time's up, but the fight goes on!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_out_of_time_win">
		<text>Victory! En got him! But wait! Wait! What is it? An didn't make it to the cancelled time And I lost! But despite this sad whimpering Yay! Our winner!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_pseudodog">
		<text>Today in the arena is a white and somewhat fluffy, but incredibly evil pseudo-dog! The pseudo-dog will be opposed by the unknown who came from nowhere!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_snork">
		<text>Today, the arena of martial arts and proper nutrition is sultry Terrible Snork The Snork will be opposed by a human A man without a past Last time he showed what he can do Let's see what happens this time</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_start">
		<text>And so... GUM! GUM! It's on!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_win_1">
		<text>Victory! You managed to put your opponent down in the time allotted and won! Hooray for our winner!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_win_2">
		<text>Victory! Hooray for our winner!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_scenario_bar_arena_megafon_mega_arena_zver">
		<text>Someone you know is in the arena tonight. Someone you love. Someone who hates you with all his wild animal nature. Yes, yes, yes! It's a terrible and invincible beast!</text>
	</string>
</string_table>