<!--
   Locale: English
   Folder: Characters_voice\dialogs
-->

<string_table>	
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_chernobyl_crush_1">
        <text>No, we had nothing to do with it. Our experiment began after the Chernobyl accident.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_death_truck_1">
		<text>This is the transport we take our agents to different parts of the zone. Agents infiltrate the stalker environment and carry out the tasks they were programmed to do without even realising it. Unfortunately, more than half of the agents die in transit as the zone is very unstable.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_osoznanie_start_11">
		<text>Hello, I see you have a lot of questions for me. Ask them and then we'll decide what to do with you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_osoznanie_start_21">
		<text>The choice is yours</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_stalker_1">
		<text>Stalker is the name of a programme to code a person to perform certain tasks. On the approaches to the centre of the zone, we've positioned several psi units. The largest of these is known to you as the brain incinerator. Anyone who tries to pass to the centre of the zone comes under our control. Then they get coded, become our agents and get a "stalker" tattoo. Spread them around the zone, we influence the course of events and keep ourselves safe. Don't forget to subscribe!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_what_about_me_1">
		<text>You're a loose cog in the machine. On one of your trips to the centre of the zone, you got too close to us. Our defences against infiltration were thought to be perfect, but you managed to find a path we didn't know existed. We couldn't let anyone else know our secret. Mankind is not yet ready to know the truth about the causes of the zone. So we immediately began coding our agents to destroy you. For some unknown reason, the equipment malfunctioned, and we didn't notice that you yourself were among the stalkers who fell under our control. As a result, you've been tasked with killing yourself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_what_is_the_zone_1">
		<text>The Zone is the result of an out of control experiment with the naosphere, the Earth's information field. We were going to tap into the naosphere to explore the possibility of influencing it. However, during the experiment, there was a breach and the energy of the Naosphere rushed to Earth, changing everything around it. That's how the anomaly you call the zone was formed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_what_next_1">
		<text>What happens next is up to you. The zone is slowly but steadily growing. Our forces are barely strong enough to contain the flow of energy from the Naosphere. You can join us. Our forces will grow, and perhaps we can take control of him. You could destroy us. Then the energy of the Naosphere would flow unimpeded into the zone. There's no telling where that would lead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_who_are_you_1">
		<text>We're THE CONSCIOUS. A group of researchers who set out to change the world. It is known that the Earth is surrounded by a special information field - the Naosphere. It is closely connected to all sentient beings on the planet and stores all their mental images. We decided to tap into the naosphere and make changes. By removing all the dark things that have spawned humanity, to make the world perfect. No human mind is powerful enough to interact with the naosphere. So we have united our consciousness.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_dialogs_oso_why_chernobyl_1">
		<text>Chernobyl NPP was the most suitable place for our experiments. Firstly, there were very few people left here after the 1986 accident, so we were able to work without a spare. Secondly, the station provided us with the energy we needed to run the plants. Thirdly, there were powerful antennas near the station, which were used in experiments to influence people's consciousness.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>