<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚ steer rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>Anyway, it's like this! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>Hey, guys, what else did I hear? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>What's up, guys, like an anecdote! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>Well, shorter! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_5">
		<text>Quiet! Quiet! That's it! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_music_1">
		<text>And now for the soul! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_music_2">
		<text>Shetchu from the bass! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_music_3">
		<text>Come on, come on, come on, come on, let me get some of that bass? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_music_4">
		<text>Let's see if the lab geek's hands are clean or not </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>One mate asks another mate. Listen, why did you go to the zone? I've been out of the cops since the lynch mob told me to hide out here. He's a bruiser, and he's gone to the cops' office. I didn't go in, but I got pulled over, as usual. And everything's wrong with them, they're dirty. No vitals, ran a red light. Yeah, well, oncoming traffic. Yeah, backwards drunk with five guns in the boot. So what's up? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_10">
		<text>They're driving around the zone in a Behemoth, real guys. So, like, they stopped to take a piss, but they just started, then bang, out of the darkness, a bloodsucker comes out and screams "Za-sasu!" The guys looked at me calmly and said, "Thank you, of course, bro, but we're only in the closet." </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_11">
		<text>Three stalkers meet at the dump, one of them has his eye out in real life, the other one has a scarred face third toe has no toe at all you know, like asking who got the beauty from where The first one shows his eye and says I'm the one who killed the guys I'm just kind of nodding respectfully, okay? The other one's pointing at his face. I'm the one who's got the pseudo-dogs on his face, I'm the one who's got the bug All right, that's fine. They're looking at the third one, who's kind of confused, so he's not saying anything You hear your mates asking what happened to your leg? I went to the camp and put on my pants so they wouldn't become patents from radiation So I put it on and the rubber band burst </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>One day a brother comes into a bar on Skadovska and says beard. Hey, bro, give me some booze, give him some booze. A glass of beer or a shot of vodka? A glass of vodka, of course. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>Stalker returned to the zone, but kind of home visited, but also complains. You hear me, I pushed an artefact and bought a Tachydlo, and she's a week away stolen. The other one said to him, "Good luck, and you went to the police went, said it wasn't them. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>The mother, in short, sends the pasan normal on kicha-malava. It's like, son, you're a mess on the housekeeping. Spring has already come, we need to dig up the vegetable garden there potatoes and other muinya to plant. I can't do shit on my own, and no fucking bitch can help me. Well, that's what the kid's telling her. Like, mother, it's great, you'd better not touch the garden at all. You're gonna dig up something that's gonna get me sentenced. And you'll be sent away covered. Mother writes a week later, "Figa sirodnoy, after your letter the cops ran to us. We dug up the whole garden, only they didn't find shit. Zli such were, maty da did not go round. And the kid says to her. Well, like mother, well, what I could, I helped, but you're not going to plant potatoes by yourself. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_intros_intro_joke_5">
		<text>Anyway, two brothers are sitting around talking. One of them says, "Hey, bro, we've been hanging out since we were kids. Let me remind you, that's not what I'm gonna do. The other one was like, oh, that's a good one. Let's kind of tank on the back, but only to be beautiful, sechyetsya, offence on the tour, and pupena will be zubdayu. Five minutes go by, the ringman's like, ovo! All right, it's done! And the other one, you don't get it, why so fast, ringman? What the fuck are all four bocles. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_6">
		<text>It's like, what's going on, where's going on, when's going on? The presenter is like this. The question will be asked by a real kid in Ivan. Ivan appears on the screen, his face like this, honourable connoisseurs. So, two months ago, my mate Kalyan took over I got five grand and he wouldn't give it to me, bitch. A month ago Kalyan borrowed three grand from me and hasn't paid me back, bitch. A week ago he only borrowed half a cent, but also, bitch, Rebane didn't. So the fucking question is, who the fuck is in the black box? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_7">
		<text>Standing like this are two particular stalker suckers in a junkyard. One sort of asks the other. Hey, I don't get it. We gave them money, we gave them money. Why aren't those boys out dancing? I've told you a hundred times you're a woodpecker. Gopac and op-stop, they're not the same shit anyway. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_8">
		<text>The guys made one of them alive, and then they gave him a crash. Oh, like, a theme, so we'll have someone to clean up our mess. And he's, like, like, a big shot, and he says, I'm not a six or a horned stag, bros. Give me something cleaner. Well, the boys were talking amongst themselves, and they said, No problem, man. Go out and get your namali, barachlozh Murikovskaya to get it. He thought about it, he thought about it, and he said. I got it, guys, where's this shit? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_jokes_joke_9">
		<text>Two bloodsuckers, one to the other. You're like a stalker on the hunt, aren't you? I notice the stalker, then I make a big circle around her in 5 for five minutes and then I attack after five more minutes, and the first one's like that I don't get it. What's the point, mate? What are you doing with these circles? You could have some meat, and the other one would be like, "I didn't pay attention to the topic, you don't know what to do You can do it right away, but then you'd have to eat it with shit </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_abuse_1">
		<text>Subtitle Editor N. Novikova Corrector A. Kulakova </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_default_1">
		<text>Subtitle Editor N. Novikova Corrector A. Kulakova </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_fight_1">
		<text>Subtitle Editor N. Novikova Corrector A. Kulakova </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Subtitle Editor N. Novikova Corrector A. Kulakova </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_1_talk_use_no_weapon_1">
		<text>Subtitle Editor N. Novikova Corrector A. Kulakova </text>
	</string>
</string_table>