<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>In short, like, why. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>Yeah, bros, what else did I hear? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>What's up, guys, like an anecdote! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>Anyway! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_5">
		<text>Quiet! Quiet! That's it! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_music_1">
		<text>And now, for the soul! </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_music_2">
		<text>Shech from the pool! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_music_3">
		<text>Come on, come on, come on, come on, let me get some of that bass? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_music_4">
		<text>Now let's see if the labouche's hands are clear or not? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>A kid comes up to the dealer Like, you want a grenade for a fiver? Chumleya, you're a dick, come on! Here you go! But for the ring, it's a hony dweeb! </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_jokes_joke_10">
		<text>I'm driving a Beech on the zone, real guys, so they stopped to take a piss bang, a bloodsucker comes out of the dark and screams I'll suck it, guys, we looked at it calmly. Thank you, bro, but we're just being casual </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_jokes_joke_11">
		<text>Meet, in short, three stalkers at the dump, one has an eye out in reality, the other face all so specifically in the scar, and the third has no toe at all. You know, like, they started asking, "Who's got this beauty? The first one shows his eye and says, I'm the one who clipped the guys, I had to shoot back. It's all kind of respectful, I guess, okay. The other one's poking his face, I'm the one who insists, I'm all in the dosobahs. It's all so respectful, normal, respectful. They look at the third one, and he's kind of confused, so he doesn't say anything. Hey, mate, what happened to your leg, I ask you? Yes, he says, he ploughed for the boys in the camp, so he put on lead pants so that he wouldn't become impotent from radiation. So I put it on, so what? It's a rubber band burst. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>A fairy came to Bodian when he was still a teenager. What a mouthful. I'm either a moznite dyke for life, and generally wacky. And a memory as clever as Umbatana's in kind. Either you're gonna be the right kid for the job. So I'm like, I'm asking him, what's up, and I'm like, what's up, what's up, and I can't remember what's up. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>so it's like a stalker crossing in the zone and actually pointing or reading like he can read to the right is like an anomaly forward monsters left taverns and chicks, so he fell forward, wondering if he'd be killed I'll have to ask the Boogers what kind of horrors are these new sensations, new sensations, new pubs and girls </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>Two stalkers are walking on a tour through the forest. Old to young here suddenly and gutturally. It's like, go slowly to that tree over there. Well, the young one did. I got up to ask what's next. And the other one's quietly asking. Is everything okay in there or what? It's kind of cool. Aaaaaaaaaaah! Awesome! I knew they were talking about that anomaly. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_intros_intro_joke_5">
		<text>So two tachyderms kissed in the zone specifically. From one encounter to the next. Anyway, we've got some fights going on here, Mahalov's showdown. And the checker's sitting on his stash, smiling. Oh, awesome! The glade's going to be covered, no shame and brother Nov is clean to the hazza. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_jokes_joke_6">
		<text>drive up to the bar, specifically two stalkers, one rasfaltsovannya on this yota, all prypantakh na tsirla, the other one on a shitty non-Verosfygazhaya, well cool, goes out in the dough and sees the other one, five minutes can not slam the door. Well, you stand next to me, look at me and say, "Why are you worried, why are you scared, who? It's always quiet here, I don't even close my sharpening machine. And the man said, "I didn't close the door for you either, so yesterday a borer took a shit on the seat. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_jokes_joke_7">
		<text>So the controller decided to specifically blind dog us shake on your hind legs. And the zombie is sitting next to him, and he's just messing around. It's like, knock it off, you're not gonna make it anyway. And close the controller, you fucking stalker, too I don't think he listened much. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_jokes_joke_8">
		<text>Three stalkers are walking along and, like, they're trying to figure out who's the coolest. The first one says, "I'm a tough guy, I've killed three bandits. And the other one, no bro, I'm way cooler, I've killed ten men. And the third one, the tonuvas are suckers, I've put a hundred of them down. And then, you hear, they see a tired-looking kid walking by, in a leather jacket so shabby, and she's whistling something, like Vladimir Central. Stalkers - oops, fell out on treason, and in the bushes hiding. Well, the kid didn't notice them, just kept walking. And they're sitting there, like, one day. Hey, guys, what's this bzlo? Second - no, well, really bzlo, what's the big deal? And the third - why are you staring at me? I'm hating you! </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_jokes_joke_9">
		<text>Two guys meet in the zone, one says to the other, "Nice hat, rat, or we'll hit you in the head for the rat, the bitch answered for the rat </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_use_abuse_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_use_no_default_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_use_no_fight_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_3_talk_use_no_weapon_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
</string_table>