<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>Anyway, it's kind of like this </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>What else have I heard? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>So, like a joke </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>Well, here's an anecdote. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_music_1">
		<text>And now for the soul. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_music_2">
		<text>There's something with Batsoy </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_music_3">
		<text>Ah, it's been a long time since I've picked up music. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_music_4">
		<text>Let me get something to eat </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_music_5">
		<text>Let's see if you've lost your moob or not. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_music_6">
		<text>One-two! All right! AND GO! </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>One mate asks the other. Hey, what are you doing in the zone? I ran away from the police station, so I thought I'd take refuge here. What'd you go to the cops for? You're welcome! Stopped as usual, everything wrong with them. Rooms are dirty, no first aid kit. Driving on red, oncoming traffic, backwards, drunk, with five guns in the boot. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>One day a bro walks into a bar on Skadovska and says, Borodia, Hey, bro, give me some booze, give him a glass of beer or a shot of vodka, fucking course, a glass of vodka. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>Back to the zone, stalker horse, after he'd been home. So he's complaining. I pushed artefacts, bought a car, it was stolen a week later. Oh, man, that's unlucky. Have you been to the police station? Yes, he was. They said they didn't. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>The mother, in short, sends the kid a kichu-malava. It's like, son, you're like an asshole in the household. Like, it's spring, we should dig up the garden, the potatoes put away. I can't do shit on my own, and no bitch can help me. Guys, I'm writing this off, you'd better mother the vegetable garden Don't touch it, or you'll dig up something that won't just be for me and you'll be sent away covered. Mother writes a week later, "Figassi, my dear, after the the cops came and dug up your letter, but they couldn't find shit, they were so angry, shouting at the sky and the boys say, "Mother, whatever I can do and you can plant your own potatoes. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_jokes_joke_5">
		<text>Two brothers sitting around talking. One of those. Hey, bro, we've been hanging out since we were kids. Let me burn you something to remember. The other one's like this. Oh, that's a good one. Let's have a potank on your back. Well, just so you're pretty. He's like. You're insulting me. It's gonna be awesome. I'll give you that. Five minutes go by. It's a ring. Awesome. Done. The other one's like this. Whoops. What's so fast? What the fuck, it's only four letters. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_jokes_joke_6">
		<text>It's like, what, where, when, the presenter is like this, and the question will be asked by a real kid in a van. Dear connoisseurs, two months ago my friend Kalyan borrowed five kosari from me and did not pay me back. A month ago Kalyan borrowed three grand from me and hasn't paid me back. A week ago he borrowed only fifty dollars, but he didn't give it back either. Anyway, the fucking question is, who's in the black box? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_jokes_joke_7">
		<text>Standing like two such a particular lochostalker on the dump, one of them asks the other like, listen, I do not understand something. We gave them money, and these guys are off somewhere not dancing? You're a peckerwood, I've told you a hundred times. Gopac and gop-stop are not the same shit anyway. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_jokes_joke_8">
		<text>So the guys made a stoker alive, and they say it's a topic of who's gonna clean our pores and he's like an old fella and says, "I'm not a six or a deer Horny, give me something cleaner. Well, the guys talked it over and said no problem. A man and a couch from the anomaly He thought about it and said, "Guys, where's the loo? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_jokes_joke_9">
		<text>two bloodsuckers are squabbling One of them was like How do you hunt stalkers? So he's like, well So I spot a stalker Then I make a big circle around it In five minutes, little one It's not until another five minutes later that I attack First one like that, I don't get it Well, what's the point, mate? Do laps, like, any way you can bowl at once And the other one was like, no bro You don't know the subject You can hit me right away, no problem Only then you'd have to eat it with shit </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_use_abuse_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_use_no_default_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_use_no_fight_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_4_talk_use_no_weapon_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
</string_table>