<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚РЎР‚ steer rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>Anyway, it's like this! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>Hey, guys, what else did I hear? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>What's up, guys, like an anecdote! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>Well, shorter! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_1">
		<text>And now for the soul! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_2">
		<text>Shetchu from the bass! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_3">
		<text>Come on, come on, come on, come on, let me get some of that bass? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_4">
		<text>Let's see if the lab geek's hands are clean or not </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>One mate asks another mate. Listen, why did you go to the zone? I've been out of the cops since the lynch mob told me to hide out here. He's a bruiser, and he's gone to the cops' office. I didn't go in, but I got pulled over, as usual. And everything's wrong with them, they're dirty. No vitals, ran a red light. Yeah, well, oncoming traffic. Yeah, backwards drunk with five guns in the boot. So what's up? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>One day a brother comes into a bar on Skadovska and says beard. Hey, bro, give me some booze, give him some booze. A glass of beer or a shot of vodka? A glass of vodka, of course. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>Stalker returned to the zone, but kind of home visited, but also complains. You hear me, I pushed an artefact and bought a Tachydlo, and she's a week away stolen. The other one said to him, "Good luck, and you went to the police went, said it wasn't them. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>The mother, in short, sends the pasan normal on kicha-malava. It's like, son, you're a mess on the housekeeping. Spring has already come, we need to dig up the vegetable garden there potatoes and other muinya to plant. I can't do shit on my own, and no fucking bitch can help me. Well, that's what the kid's telling her. Like, mother, it's great, you'd better not touch the garden at all. You're gonna dig up something that's gonna get me sentenced. And you'll be sent away covered. Mother writes a week later, "Figa sirodnoy, after your letter the cops ran to us. We dug up the whole garden, only they didn't find shit. Zli such were, maty da did not go round. And the kid says to her. Well, like mother, well, what I could, I helped, but you're not going to plant potatoes by yourself. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_5">
		<text>Anyway, two brothers are sitting around talking. One of them says, "Hey, bro, we've been hanging out since we were kids. Let me remind you, that's not what I'm gonna do. The other one was like, oh, that's a good one. Let's kind of tank on the back, but only to be beautiful, sechyetsya, offence on the tour, and pupena will be zubdayu. Five minutes go by, the ringman's like, ovo! All right, it's done! And the other one, you don't get it, why so fast, ringman? What the fuck are all four bocles. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_6">
		<text>It's like, what's going on, where's going on, when's going on? The presenter is like this. The question will be asked by a real kid in Ivan. Ivan appears on the screen, his face like this, honourable connoisseurs. So, two months ago, my mate Kalyan took over I got five grand and he wouldn't give it to me, bitch. A month ago Kalyan borrowed three grand from me and hasn't paid me back, bitch. A week ago he only borrowed half a cent, but also, bitch, Rebane didn't. So the fucking question is, who the fuck is in the black box? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_7">
		<text>Standing like this are two particular stalker suckers in a junkyard. One sort of asks the other. Hey, I don't get it. We gave them money, we gave them money. Why aren't those boys out dancing? I've told you a hundred times you're a woodpecker. Gopac and op-stop, they're not the same shit anyway. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_8">
		<text>The guys made one of them alive, and then they gave him a crash. Oh, like, a theme, so we'll have someone to clean up our mess. And he's, like, like, a big shot, and he says, I'm not a six or a horned stag, bros. Give me something cleaner. Well, the boys were talking amongst themselves, and they said, No problem, man. Go out and get your namali, barachlozh Murikovskaya to get it. He thought about it, he thought about it, and he said. I got it, guys, where's this shit? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_9">
		<text>Two bloodsuckers, one to the other. You're like a stalker on the hunt, aren't you? I notice the stalker, then I make a big circle around her in 5 for five minutes and then I attack after five more minutes, and the first one's like that I don't get it. What's the point, mate? What are you doing with these circles? You could have some meat, and the other one would be like, "I didn't pay attention to the topic, you don't know what to do You can do it right away, but then you'd have to eat it with shit </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_abuse_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_default_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_fight_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_weapon_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Music! Music! Music! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>Anyway, it's kind of like this </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>What else have I heard? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>What's up, like an anecdote! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>Well, here's an anecdote. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_1">
		<text>And now for the soul! </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_2">
		<text>I'm gonna get something with Batsoy </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_3">
		<text>Ah, it's been a long time since I've picked up music. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_4">
		<text>How about I give you something with bats? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_5">
		<text>Let's see if you've lost your moob or not. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_music_6">
		<text>One-two! All right! AND GO! </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_1">
		<text>One mate asks the other. Hey, what are you doing in the zone? I ran away from the police station, so I thought I'd take refuge here. What'd you go to the cops for? You're welcome! Stopped as usual, everything wrong with them. Rooms are dirty, no first aid kit. Driving red, oncoming, backwards, drunk. With drinking boots in the boot. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_2">
		<text>One day a bro walks into a bar on Skadovska and says Borodja, bro, give me some booze, give him a drink a glass of beer or a shot of vodka, fuck, of course, a glass of vodka. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_3">
		<text>Back, Lasha rastalker to the zone after the house has been visited. So he's complaining. I pushed artefacts, bought a car, it was stolen a week later. Oh, man, that's unlucky. Have you been to the police station? Yes, he was. They said they didn't. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_intros_intro_joke_4">
		<text>The mother, in short, sends the kid a kichu-malava. It's like, son, you're like an asshole in the household. Like, it's spring, we should dig up the garden, the potatoes put away. I can't do shit on my own, and no bitch can help me. The kid's texting her back. You'd better not touch the garden, Mum. You're gonna dig up something that's gonna get me more than just jail time, and they'll send you away covered. Mother writes a week later, "Figassi, my dear, after the the cops came and dug up your letter, only they didn't find shit. They were so angry, they were bending swear words to the sky, and the kid was like he says, like, mother, whatever I can do to help. You can plant your own potatoes. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_5">
		<text>Two brothers sitting around talking. One of those, Hey, bro, We've been hanging out since we were kids. Let me burn you something to remember. The other one's like this, Oh, that's a good one, Let's tank on your back. Well, just so you're pretty, He's like, Running, It's gonna be awesome. Five minutes go by. It's a ring, Awesome, Done. The other one's like this, Whoops, What's so fast? What the fuck, It's only four letters. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_6">
		<text>It's like what's going on, where, when, the presenter's like, what's the question? will be asked by a real kid in a van. Dear experts, two months ago, my mate Kalyan borrowed five grand from me and didn't give it back. A month ago Kalyan borrowed three grand from me and hasn't paid me back. A week ago he borrowed only fifty dollars, but he didn't give it back either. Anyway, the fucking question is, who's in the black box?  </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_7">
		<text>There's, like, two of these particular lochostalkers standing in a junkyard. One asks the other type. Hey, I don't get it. We gave them money, and then these guys go off somewhere don't dance. You're a peckerwood, I've told you a hundred times. Gopac and gopstop are not the same floor crap anyway. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_8">
		<text>The boys made one stolkeruga alive, and they said, Oh, like a theme, so we'll have someone to clean up our shit. And he's like, like, he's an old fella, he didn't catch it and he says, bro, I'm not a six or a horny deer, give me something cleaner. Well, the guys got into it and said, "No problem, man, go ahead out of the anomaly of the Murikowska barracks. He thought about it, thought about it, and said, "Well, guys, where is this latrine? </text>
	</string>
	<!-- Accuracy Check Needed -->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_jokes_joke_9">
		<text>two bloodsuckers are talking, one to the other like, "How do you hunt stalkers? I noticed the stalker, then I made a big circle around him. After five minutes small, and only after another five minutes attacking. First one, I don't get it, what's the point, mate? What's the point of these circles, like, at any rate, you can immediately bowl for khazhivat, and the other one is like, like, no bro, you don't know the topic. You can hit him right away, no question, but then you'll have to eat his shit. </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_abuse_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_default_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_fight_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_sleep_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
	<!--Silent-->
	<string id="as_sub_characters_voice_human_bandit_2_talk_use_no_weapon_1">
		<text>Silent_Subtitle </text>
	</string>
</string_table>